if you are a coach online the reason why
you want to do group coaching is because
you are limited by the amount of hours
that you work if you are doing
one-on-one coaching is the way that you
make money and the way that you can
actually scale a business while removing
yourself from it from a Time perspective
gaining your time back is by going into
a group setting with multiple people my
name is Jeremiah Kowski and for the last
21 years I've been helping the world's
best coaches trainers and mentors scale
their businesses to 10 T of millions of
dollars online I've personally built
multiple coaching businesses over $10
million per year in profit and I help
people that are just getting started how
to make their first5 to 25 $30,000 a
month with group coaching programs and
so that's what I'm going to be talking
about here today is how to actually
structure a group coaching program how
to put it all together what the best
practices are and then why you actually
can serve people better inside of a
group coaching program than you do with
one-on-one coaching so just case in
point the amount of hours you work if go
one-on-one you are limited by I show up
oneon-one with somebody and that's all I
get to do when you do group coaching you
can have a group of people and still
charge pretty close to the same as what
you would for one-on-one coaching and
that's one of the misconceptions people
think is they're like well group
coaching is going to be lower quality
because it's a group fact is when you
know how to do it the way that I'm going
to show you in this video you're
actually going to serve your clients
better and we hear often from people
that they actually got served better
inside of group programs like like my
client growth accelerator program than
they did in one-on-one coaching with
other clients and it's one of the first
things that you have to learn is that
your desire to get everybody the result
and control the outcome by connecting
one-on-one with everybody that need for
doing
it perfectly with everybody as far as
that goes that need comes from a good
place and I get that but it's
financially hurting you because you're
limiting yourself by what feels
comfortable and by what feels like you
can continue to do it in a controlled
environment when you go into a group
setting you end up letting go of control
because there's a lot of people that are
inside of a group that they will choose
to not necessarily do what you say to do
and you don't have control over what
every single person does otherwise
you're going to step into codependency
and that's not healthy at all and I
don't want to encourage anybody to do
that because that's a recipe for Burnout
and failure and your clients are going
to like it as well so what you got to do
is you got to learn to get more specific
when you do one-on-one coaching you
might help people that have a lot of
different issues find the golden thread
pattern across all of them that they
have in common and that's what you can
build a group coaching program around
and so take a look at what is the
solution that you help people with
inside of your one-on-one coaching and
then what do the most of those people
have in common that they need solved and
and again this is going to address
inside of you what you might feel
uncomfortable with well I don't want to
limit myself I don't want to limit who I
can work with I get it and I understand
it because I was one of those people
that thought that same way but the truth
is you're limiting yourself from being
able to actually impact people to the
level that you are capable by only doing
oneon-one coaching and even selling hour
like sessions like sessions at a time as
far as that goes okay so what you want
to do in your business is you got to
have a Val value ladder that's one of
the first things that you want to do and
the value ladder is this right you have
free content that you might deliver that
could be something like YouTube channel
that could be like your social media
content then you have your paid and this
could be like low ticket low cost
entrylevel
products these entry level products
might be under $97 right here and then
your group programs will start
at500 upward to $2500 right here okay
and so that's what we call a mid ticket
group coaching program you might be able
to throw a couple hundred people into
this right here and have a multi six
figure business that's incredible as far
as that goes now the next phase Above
This is where we throw in high ticket
where we go 6,000 to uh $10,000 as far
as the cost goes and this is more of a
high ticket program these are for people
that maybe graduate from this level and
they need more specialized expertise as
far as that goes okay and so this is the
value letter that a lot of coaches need
to do and they need to get out of the
trading dollars for hours employee
mindset service provider mindset that
they they come into the game with so
focused on well I I work this many hours
and I get paid this much realize and you
got to put on a CEO hat look at your
business as a CEO as a business owner as
somebody who is an owner not just
somebody who is operating not just
somebody who is necessarily doing a
service for people but somebody who
takes a look at it like a real
legitimate business owner and the way
that a business owner looks at it is how
do we leverage our our our inputs to get
the most output and so by bringing
people into a group where you charge
them specifically at a group rate you're
able to leverage your time to where you
can show up um in front of the group
instead of having to be one-on-one
individual with people okay now the way
that you serve people better when it
comes to the group is that you're going
to base this off of the feedback of the
group okay and so this is one of the
biggest mistakes that I mean a lot of
coaches that they make that they're so
focused in on well I just you know
everybody's different they're all
different they all have this yes they
are all different but when you come into
a group you want to listen to what do
they all have in common the people that
are coming into your group what are the
main common factors that they share
together when it comes to how they're
going to need to be served what are the
problems that they all share again you
might have 500 people that are all very
different from each other that's normal
okay but there all 500 of those people
might share a common issue like in my
business they're struggling to finish
their landing pages they want to know
how to get their Facebook ads out they
want to know how to attract more clients
and work Less hours and what is the best
way to be able to serve their clients
better this is what I solve with my
clients in my accelerator every single
week we help them with their messaging
their marketing their sales processes so
that they can actually semi-retire and
don't even have to work as many hours
make way more money while serving people
at an exceptionally higher level and so
once you can break up with the need to
control the outcome inside of your
client's lives please you need to do
that you need to graduate from a place
where you are trying to control the
outcome that your clients get get and
you get to the place where yes you're
going to serve them at a high level
you're going to serve them excellently
but you are okay
with only a percentage of your group
getting the big picture result that
you're going to sell to people okay and
listen that's not a popular statement to
say but I've been in this industry for
21 years and the people that can do this
and they can resolve inside of
themselves that tension of well I need
to get everybody the perfect highest
level result and you can resolve that
inside of yourself so that you can show
up to a group and you're not limiting
yourself by the amount of hours that you
have out of a need to control the
outcome inside of in front of
everybody's businesses and their lives
or whatever you help people with and
you're able to get people into a
container around a specific focus a
specific issue Focus that you help the
group with as far as this goes you know
I can help coach people on a lot of
different things but I'm going to focus
on
two specific areas in my business that's
what you want to focus on when you have
a
group is what is the area that I can
make the most amount of money with right
here and then combined with that also
create the highest level of impact with
people and you want these to converge
finances and impact to where the most
amount of money are people are willing
to consistently invest with you to pay
you and it's able to produce the highest
level of result with your clients impact
is important but you don't have a
business unless you are bringing in
finances and that's one of the biggest
mistakes that I meet that a lot of
people make is that they are they're way
too focused on this impact side of
things because that's what every Guru
out there says to do but they don't have
a business and they're not actually
impacting people because they don't
actually have people buying from them
and now they're struggling to get
clients because they don't have an
income and now they're burning out and
so the so it's a it's a it's a
misbalanced
focus by only focusing in on impact now
if you only focus in on finances you're
also going to struggle because you're
not going to give people results so we
want to balance these two and hold a
balance and attention of these as far as
that goes what you do and you facilitate
inside of your programs inside of a
group program is that people will give
you their feedback as to what they are
struggling with what they need help with
what are the areas that they want you to
work with them on what are those areas
that they need the most help with you
you facilitate inside of the group
people telling you what it is that they
are struggling with and then you pay
attention to what are the patterns that
they all have in common and then that's
where you build out your marketing side
of things okay so when it comes to
facilitating the group you're going to
look at and start to get people to tell
you what the things that they want to
learn are as a group they will start to
tell you a common area of things and
what you're going to notice is going to
happen is that there's going to be a
segment of the group that's going to
drop off you're going to have drop off
right here drop off is a good thing when
it comes to group coaching why because
you're getting more specific more
specific more specific to the best
people these ones right here that you
want to work with and you're eliminating
the ones that are not necessarily going
to fall into these two categories and
what ends up happening is your profit
margins start going up because you start
focusing in on your rock stars and your
Superstars and the ones that are
actually starting to get the most
results with you again this goes way
against the normal way if you are
certified in coaching or you've been
trained in coaching you come from
traditional education as to what they
teach you how to do but this is how
you're going to make the most amount of
financial income for yourself to be able
to create multiple six figures and not
have to work more than 10 hours a week
to be able to do so as you figure out
what do those rock stars need help with
the most and you start structuring all
of your content inside of your group
coaching around that and so you can
create courses you can do uh group
sessions you can do group Q&A you can
create trainings for your group that
solve the issues that the main top rock
stars have there's going to be people
that are going to be like well I don't
feel served anymore because I'm not a
rock
star great let them
leave out the door help them out the
door as far as that goes you get it
again not a lot of people get this
because again this goes against what
we're told we should do it makes people
feel uncomfortable you got to deal with
whatever that thing is inside of you
that's feeling uncomfortable about
people leaving your program because
you're focusing on the best group of
people that's going to make you the most
amount of money and impact okay so when
you can resolve that inside of yourself
now we can go to work to Market to more
of these people because we're no longer
going to try to attract
everybody we're going to try to attract
people that fit into this category right
here and this amplifies everything by
focusing in on that category and so we
take a look at what are the best people
that we're working with what are the
issues that they have what are the
struggles that they have and how can we
solve those problems and then what we do
is we're able to put content out there
we're able to we're able to create live
events that are that are free or low
cost that can attract more of those
people to us that fit into those
categories and then you're going to have
is you're going to have a compounding
income effect where month over month
over month you might start off where
you're going to
have you know you might have 10 people
at $97 a month so that's going to be
$970 but then the next month you might
have 30 people and now we're at almost
$3,000 right here okay at $100 a month
as far as that goes
$100 a month program that's about $1,200
a year okay and so as you start to
compound you might add 20 people a month
to this this starts to compound and over
time you'll be able to have in a group
the income starts to increase and you
don't have to do any extra work you
don't have to meet with any extra people
and so that's one of the biggest reasons
why a group coaching program is so
important is because you you can create
a system for yourself where you
consistently do the same work each month
with with the group as it grows but your
income level starts to go up
because the amount of people that you
have coming in goes up in the group okay
and so that's what we want to focus on
is we want to look at what are those
areas of the people that are getting the
most impact that are also spending the
most amount of money with us then how do
we bring in more of those people into
our programs okay and so when it comes
to creating a program like that you got
to learn how to be a leader of a group
this is a different skill than working
one-on-one with people learning how to
communicate with a group of people by
listening to what does the group have
you're not going to be able to help
every single issue inside of the group
all at once because you're only one
person but you can pay attention to what
the patterns that they have are what are
the patterns of issues or problems or
struggles or frustrations that the group
has and then you can create content
trainings courses and accountability
materials workbooks whatever it is based
around that and so that now becomes your
ecosystem inside of the group to help
people one of the biggest mistakes that
I see a lot of people make is that
they're trying to build a coaching
business just doing oneon-one and then
they say once I master that then I'll go
to group coaching I get it that's a
great way to struggle for years and
years and years and and not kind of see
the returns that you
want so it's better for most people to
actually go into group coaching is what
I recommend is that they go into this
and they and they start by not um not
trying
to not like they they can start by not
necessarily trying to
to get all the people that are in
there to the top you're got you got to
realize you're not going to get
everybody to the
top they're not always going to get
there you're going to have some people
that are going to drop off okay and so
you might be asking Jeremiah can you
show me how to do this well inside of my
group coaching program the client growth
accelerator that's what I work with
people on is I show them how to do this
I show them exact how to structure a
program like this how to build a program
like this and how to help people every
single day inside of their programs we
have clients right now that are making
tens of thousands of dollars inside of
their programs using our system that
they can attract clients to them and
close sales and I've been doing this for
21 years helping people do this
successfully is it a
risk shifting out of one-on-one coaching
if it's something that you've never done
before is it is it going to be something
that maybe feels a little little bit
uncomfortable
possibly but that's why it's good to get
into a community of people that are
actually working towards a common goal
together that you can grow with together
as far as that goes okay and so the way
that we Market it is we can Market the
result and the outcome that the group
has in common when we want to Market a
program like this and you sell it as a
group program you sell it as a group
coaching program you might have people
that still want one-on-one coaching and
now you want to charge more for that
$10,000 $220,000 for the one-on-one
coaching based on the people that have
already come through the group program
okay so one of the biggest issues that
people have is that they they they're
just they're trying to do it all and
they're trying to help everybody so
deeply inside of the group that it steps
into this kind of toxic codependency
type of a thing to where they're not
able to actually help people because
they're not showing up at their best
they're showing up trying to just tread
water and serve everybody's needs and
desires all at once instead of saying
okay what is the one issue Focus that
this whole group in common has then how
can I serve that and how can I solve
that for people now one of the biggest
mistakes that you can make is don't just
have a course don't just sell a course a
course by itself is just information a
group coaching program can include
training but it also provides
accountability and support and you can
help the group as a whole to get result
results and so one of the number one
things that you want to make sure of
that you're doing is that you are
gathering people in front of you that
you're getting practiced by doing this
and this is why hosting Live Events this
is why posting on social media this is
why creating content Say on YouTube or
your or your Instagram or Facebook is a
great way to attract people to you to
your coaching business okay that's one
of the ways that we encourage people to
do is to is to use social media to bring
in their clients and what you want to do
is you want to find what is the common
thread pattern that the people in the
group have that are problems that
they're dealing with and then how can we
create pieces of content material for
people that are out there in the public
that have those same problems so then
what you get to do is you get to show
and demonstrate that you know how to
solve those problems for people and you
can bring them in and by demonstrating
that to them now we can bring them in as
a client to a group program okay the way
you want to price your group program
like I said $500 to $2,500 you can also
do a monthly payment on that 5050 to 100
bucks a month 200 bucks a month and
people pay you monthly to jump into a
program with you where you provide
support training accountability work
with them through their problems to help
them solve the issues that they have so
decide on what is your Niche what topic
do you help people with figure out what
is that Common Thread pattern that
people have and then you can bring them
into a program with you to solve those
problems okay and so that's what I help
people with in our accelerator programs
I help them go through how to figure out
how do we put one of these together how
do we actually Market people how do we
run Facebook ads how do we create
content to attract people to us into our
programs and then how do we sell these
programs to people that are that are
needing to solve the problems that we
solve in our Pro in our in our group
coaching programs okay so we put
together a program and then we put
together marketing materials and we put
together sales information and how to
sell and present to people and promote
to them what it is that we solv the
problem with
and so when you can learn how to
communicate in a way that draws people
to you you can learn to show up with
confidence and you can learn to present
it in a way that that demonstrates the
value that you have and and and you get
out of your head of trying to please
everybody trying to get everybody's
approval you realize that not everybody
this is not going to be a a Baskin
Robbins good fit for everybody that you
meet that's out there that's
okay at the end of the day what you want
to do is you want to find the ones that
are the gold the goldm clients the
soulmate clients the ones that are meant
to work with you the ones that are good
fit for what you have to offer and the
ones that are a really good fit for what
you have to offer they're going to
resonate with you your message how you
help people to come in to your programs
to get the results that you want and so
it's all about getting good at pattern
recognition it's all about identifying
the of the people that we're working
with what are the common thread issues
that they all have in common what are
the main struggles or the main
frustrations what are the main desires
and drivers and motivators of why people
want help why people want coaching why
people want to move forward and then you
can build something around that you
build your marketing materials you build
your landing pages you build your lead
magnets you start to grow in email list
in the community online and an audience
of people around a specific issue and
then you lead them to go purchase a
program that you have that is a group
program okay so if you want to work with
me to help you put this together get
clients and start to kind of make the
kind of money that you want to make 5 to
$25 $30,000 per month consistently in
your business I'd love to work with you
on that in my accelerator program I'd
love to see you in there we'll talk soon
have a good one everybody